<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Top</string>
    <string name="article_thumbnail">article thumbnail</string>
    <string name="food">Food</string>
    <string name="technology">Technology</string>
    <string name="travel">Travel</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="large_thumbnail">large_thumbnail</string>
    <string name="ipsum">Croque monsieur rubber cheese say cheese. Cheese on toast cut the cheese paneer cheese on toast manchego feta dolcelatte red leicester. Pepper jack who moved my cheese red leicester chalk and cheese cheese on toast lancashire smelly cheese cheese and wine. Who moved my cheese cheese on toast macaroni cheese emmental hard cheese mozzarella. Mozzarella queso mozzarella. Melted cheese jarlsberg boursin cheddar squirty cheese danish fontina parmesan ricotta. Cheddar cheese strings cheesy feet airedale cottage cheese squirty cheese stinking bishop cheese triangles. Cheeseburger port-salut macaroni cheese cheese and wine paneer blue castello manchego. Manchego ricotta fromage. Dolcelatte bocconcini cheesy grin cottage cheese cheese strings squirty cheese cottage cheese cheese and biscuits. Halloumi macaroni cheese fondue everyone loves when the cheese comes out everybody\'s happy cheese on toast fromage cheddar. Queso fromage frais pepper jack. Cheese slices stilton st. agur blue cheese. Lancashire caerphilly ricotta croque monsieur taleggio fromage frais swiss croque monsieur. When the cheese comes out everybody\'s happy blue castello macaroni cheese cheese and biscuits melted cheese mascarpone port-salut macaroni cheese. Feta chalk and cheese pepper jack goat cheese triangles. Everyone loves cheesecake cheddar. Croque monsieur cheesy grin paneer brie port-salut macaroni cheese brie monterey jack. Caerphilly brie taleggio cheesy feet dolcelatte brie goat caerphilly. Taleggio bavarian bergkase airedale squirty cheese feta.</string>
</resources>
